that is coming very cool Listen to what
que viene muy Guay Escucha lo que ha
Paz Padilla has said I don't know why I don't know what it is
dicho Paz Padilla no sé por qué no sé a
due to I don't know what she wants to say with
qué se debe no sé qué querrá decir con
this but there she has launched it that I think
esto pero ahí la ha lanzado que yo creo
that many times Marina when
que muchas veces Marina que cuando se
these messages are launched they have ulterior
lanzan estos mensajes van con segundas
motives I bank on something that is recent and it goes
intenciones banco algo que reciente y va
for something that has hurt her and she wants to get
por algo que le ha dolido y que quiere
the message across to the person to
hacerle llegar el mensaje a la persona a
whom she is transmitting it save
la que se la está transmitiendo guárdate
the good wines for bad
los buenos vinos para las malas
occasions because for good
ocasiones porque para las buenas
occasions all wines are good
ocasiones todos los vinos son buenos
when you have a problem when you
cuando tú tienes un problema cuando
really need the support of people
realmente necesita el apoyo de la gente
people disappear that is why it is very good
la gente desaparece por eso es muy bueno
that sometimes things happen to do a
que a veces sucedan cosas para hacer una
screening and do a cleaning my mother
criba y hacer una limpieza mi madre
used to say that the [ __ ] of a year in the
decía que la de un año en la
kitchen is removed in one day and It is that
cocina con un día se quita y Es que a
sometimes when there is prosperity and everything
veces cuando hay prosperidad y todo
works and everything is going well She is surrounded by
funciona y todo va bien Está rodeada de
people but how many stay for when
gente pero cuánto se quedan para cuando
you need it there you discover the good
tú lo necesitas ahí descubres el buen
friend I know if publicly the
amigo yo sé si públicamente los medios
media associates this news with
de comunicación asocian esta noticia a
something she will come out to sprout on her
algo ella va a salir a brotar en sus
social networks from
redes sociales des